<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<doc target="home">
  <transcript lang="en">
    <extract id="tagline">
      Pastries, baked goodies &lt;br /&gt;and all things cake!
    </extract>

    <extract id="welcome">
      Hello &amp; Welcome to Epi de Dieu Ltée
    </extract>

    <extract id="intro">
      Epi de Dieu ltée creates amazing pastries and treats, delivering throughout Quatre-Bornes and the vicinity. Our cakes are made to order and can cater for your imagination.
    </extract>

    <extract id="events">
      Epi de Dieu can create cakes for:
    </extract>

    <extract id="wedding">
      Weddings
    </extract>

    <extract id="birthday">
      Birthdays
    </extract>
    
    <extract id="corporate">
      Corporate events
    </extract>
    
    <extract id="special">
      Special occasions
    </extract>

    <extract id="create">
      Whether you want a five tier wedding cake for your special day, a unique birthday cake for a one to one hundred year old, corporate cupcakes for a launch event, or you just fancy some cupcakes for the weekend. Epi de Dieu can create a special memorable cake just for you.
    </extract>

    <extract id="click">
      Click on one of the cake icons below and see which cake takes your fancy? There is something for everyone, and who doesn't like cake?
    </extract>

    <extract id="visit">
      Visit us and try our delicious range
    </extract>

    <extract id="time">
      Take time out of your busy day and treat yourself to some sweetness.
    </extract>

    <extract id="fb">
      Like us on Facebook
    </extract>

    <extract id="contact">
      Contact Epi de Dieu Ltd
    </extract>
  </transcript>


  <transcript lang="fr">
    <extract id="tagline">
      Patisseries, sucreries &lt;br /&gt;et gâteaux!
    </extract>

    <extract id="Bonjour">
      Hello &amp; Bienvenue à Épi de Dieu Ltée
    </extract>

    <extract id="intro">
      Épi de Dieu Ltée crée pâtisseries et gourmandises, operant aux alentours des Quatre Bornes.Nos gâteaux sont faits sur commande et mesure, tout en portant attention à l'imagination et la créativité.
    </extract>

    <extract id="events">
      Epi de Dieu entreprend pour:
    </extract>

    <extract id="wedding">
      Mariages
    </extract>

    <extract id="birthday">
      Anniversaires
    </extract>
    
    <extract id="corporate">
      Événements d'entreprise
    </extract>
    
    <extract id="special">
      Occasions spéciales
    </extract>

    <extract id="create">
      Que ce soit gâteau de mariage specialement conçu à cinq étages, gâteau d'anniversaire unique a tout âge, cupcakes pour lancement de produits ou pour concocter un bon petit week-end, Épi de Dieu vous rendera l'experience inoubliable.
    </extract>

    <extract id="click">
      Cliquez sur l'une des icônes de gâteaux sous-dessus et laissez parler vos fantasmes gastronomiques!Il y en a toujours pour tout le monde.Qui n'aime pas les gâteaux? 
    </extract>

    <extract id="visit">
      Visitez nous and goutez à notre gamme de produits.
    </extract>

    <extract id="time">
      Extrayez du temps hors de votre journée et faites vous-même plaisir avec nos sucreries.
    </extract>

    <extract id="fb">
      Vous pouvez toujours 'Aimer' notre page Facebook.
    </extract>

    <extract id="contact">
      Contactez Épi de Dieu Ltée.
    </extract>
  </transcript>
</doc>